# *Rohit Nayya*r

Milton, Ontario, rohitnayyar54@gmail.com, +1 519 709 8069

## **Objective**

Able to utilize my experience and education to create a safety driven work environment and ensure Industry compliant standards for safety In the workplace, Strong planner and problem solver who readily adapts to change works Independently and exceeds expectations.

## **Work Experience**

## Civil Carpenter

North America Construction (Erin) October 2022 to Present

- Build, layout and execute wooden forms and advanced formwork systems as required, according to specifications with the ability to make calculations depending on grades
- Ensure forms are properly designed and on grade to meet construction specifications for the project.
- Assist to build formwork, braces, other misc. carpentry
- Assist to place, set, and finish slabs and sidewalks
- Handling and transporting materials (e.g. cement, wood, tools, equipment)

## Senior Carpenter

Markstone landscaping- Burlington, ON

August 2022 to October

- Read and interpret blueprints, drawings and sketches to determine specifications and calculate requirements Prepare layouts in conformance to building codes, using measuring tool.
- Measure, cut, shape, assemble and join materials made of wood, wood substitutes, lightweight steel and other materials

#### Carpenter

Fuhrious Construction Ltd. - Lower Mainland, BC

March 2021 to August 2022

- Assists to build and install woodwork, scaffolding and braces
- Assist to build formwork, braces, other misc. carpentry
- Assist to place, set, and finish slabs and sidewalks
- Handling and transporting materials (e.g. cement, wood, tools, equipment)
- Conduct repair work and installation of slabs, sidewalks, curbs, other concrete works as required.
- Handling and transporting materials (e.g. cement, wood, tools, equipment)
- Help with setting up and transferring temporary structures (e.g. scaffolding)

#### Amazon Delivery Driver

Rev Courier Services Ltd. - Surrey, BC

July 2021 to November 2021

#### ❖ Warehouse Helper

Tepperman's - London, ON

December 2020 to March 2021

• Assembling various furniture products opicking and staging products for outbound shuttles oproper handling of all products oworking with little supervision

#### Welder

Bell Camp Manufacturing Inc - Ingersoll, ON July 2019 to October 2020

- Lay out reference points and patterns. Assemble and fit plates and sections to form structures
- Weld or bolt sections together
- Set up and operate heavy duty metal working machines

## ❖ Food handler Supervisor

South St. Burger - London, ON

May 2017 to December 2019

- Ensuring a clean and safe work environment
- Following and making recipes efficiently and effectively
- Operating large-volume cooking equipment such as grills, and deep fryers.

Food handler Supervisor

February 2020 - Stratford, Ontario

- Preparing food rotation labels and labeling all food items accordingly

#### ❖ Banquet Server

DoubleTree by Hilton - London, ON January 2017 to April 2018

Create memorable experiences with attentive service, product knowledge and a friendly attitude o Ensure all
meeting rooms, breaks, meals are set up for the required time and to the proper standards o Provide
prompt, courteous and efficient food & beverage service for functions o Effectively handle guest concerns
through a Making it Right attitude

DoubleTree by Hilton - London, ON January 2017 to April 2018

- Ensure a clean and safe working environment at all times
- Ensure all meeting rooms, breaks, and meals are set up for the required time and to the proper standards
- Work as part of a team to provide a consistently high standard of service

#### Education

Two year Diploma in Hospitality hotel and resort service management

Fanshawe College - London, ON January 2017 to April 2018

# Certification

- Working at Heights.
- Mobile elevating work platforms

### **Skills**

Excellent communication and interpersonal skills, time management and decision making skills, Team player.